[mellow music playing]
[Hina sobbing loudly]
[Ayame] This is the first time
I'm seeing someone cry this hard.
All 'cause I had to stick my nose
in her business.
But, apparently,
they have some spares back in the gym.
Could you get one for me?
If I hadn't tried to get
the two of them alone together...
What are you supposed to say to someone
at a time like this?
If I were her and someone said,
"There are better guys out there,"
I'd go, "Yeah? Let's see them then."
And if they said,
"This must be hard for you,"
it'd probably make me think,
"How could you know what I'm feeling?"
[Hina continues sobbing]
[Ayame] And anyway, I don't even know
what it's like to have a broken heart.
What should I do?
[rustling]
Why're you lining up tissues?
I thought the barbecue would be messy,
so I brought a bunch of them.
I am the manager.
They're all yours if you want.
Thank you, Ayame.
[Ayame] Let it all out. Don't hold it in.
[Hina] Okay.
[Ayame] You really like him, don't you?
[Hina] Yeah.
[continues sobbing]
[Ayame] Does Inota have any idea
that she likes him this much?
Looking back on all the guys
who've asked me out,
I wonder if any of them ever liked me
as much as she likes him.
Nope. I guess not.
I know this must be painful,
but she really fell for someone,
and I envy her for that.
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
[Coach] Now, the bus home leaves at 5 p.m.
EPISODE 25
EVEN SO
And we'll run scrimmages till then.
So, pack your stuff now.
That's a fun pattern.
It's my younger sister's.
[Taiki gasps]
[inaudible]
[Taiki] Hey.
I'm gonna head to the gym.
Practice isn't for half an hour.
I wanna practice my serves.
Sure, man.
[serene music playing]
[grunts]
[shuttlecock thudding]
[Taiki] I did the right thing.
It would've hurt her more
if I hadn't made things clear.
I told you that I'm fine with it!
[grunts softly]
- [Haryu] In.
- [gasps]
You're going at it like
we haven't been practicing for three days.
I'd never win
if a few days of practice tired me out.
[Haryu chuckles] I like what I'm hearing.
So then...
You wanna play a match against me?
- Love all. Play.
- Here's to a good game.
Hey, Kyo, do you mind
going to wake up Nishida?
Yeah, sounds good.
GLOOMY
[Ayame] I meddled
in other people's business.
I had no idea
things would turn out this way.
What's the matter?
[Ayame gasps]
[grunts angrily]
How about it's none of your business,
Kyo Kasahara?
Just stay out of it,
you nosy, meddling four-eyes!
Just a shot in the dark, but...
is this about Taiki and Hina?
Um... Uh...
You know about that?
I thought something was up with them.
They've been acting weird since yesterday.
That means Taiki gave her his answer.
[shuttlecock thudding]
[both grunting]
[emotional music playing]
Eight, four.
[pants] Darn it.
[girl 1] So it's the last time
we're going down this road, huh?
[girl 2] Let's make
this last practice count.
I just can't seem
to wrap my head around it.
Like, this is the first that I'm hearing
Inota has feelings for somebody.
What the heck?
[Kyo] Uh...
Anyway...
finding someone who'll fall
head over heels for you like Hina-bean,
it doesn't happen every day.
This would all make sense
if he had no interest in her,
but as friends, they get along so well.
I don't get it.
Well, I do. They're really good friends.
Hina would be upset
if she heard me say this, but...
I think that those two make more sense
if they're just close friends.
[Ayame exclaims]
[groans]
Taiki prefers to pursue a crush.
I don't think he's used to being pursued.
I guess caring for someone as a friend
and caring about them
as a romantic partner
are two different things.
[Ayame] Hmm.
- It is what it is.
- [exclaims]
You say that like it's no big deal.
It's all I can say.
You and I are on the sidelines,
not the field.
Taiki made his choice.
[both grunting]
[Taiki] A straight shot.
No, a cross-court.
Thirteen, six.
[exhales heavily]
[Taiki] He's not letting me score at all.
I've been wondering
why he wouldn't play me lately.
He went and got even better.
I want to catch up to him.
I don't want to lose.
If Haryu can become a stronger player,
then I can get better too.
Better! Way better!
[grunts]
[Haryu] Out!
Game, set, match.
Thanks for the practice.
Wait, what?
One more game.
Yeah, I figured you would say that.
Nah, we're done here.
And it's the last day
of training camp, after all. I'm tired.
One game's not fair.
[sighs]
Listen, being honest...
I was actually kinda nervous
to play against you.
What?
This guy? Afraid?
Embarrassing, right?
After everything,
I was never able to beat Hyodo.
That jerk had to go and quit
before I was done with him.
And then, I couldn't beat
that first-year Yusa in a practice match.
I thought if I lost to you
on top of all of that,
I wouldn't have a drop of confidence left.
[mellow music playing]
Well, in the end, I always win.
[sighs heavily]
[sighs]
I'm glad we played each other.
Besides, if I had kept putting it off,
that'd be so pathetic.
Being afraid of losing,
having my stupid pride torn to pieces...
I have to make my own peace with it,
reflect on it,
and use it to keep moving forward.
That's what makes a strong player,
to me, anyway.
Everybody is so strong.
What do you mean?
- You're strong too.
- [gasps]
[music fades]
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
- Chinatsu.
- [exclaims]
Taiki. Hey, welcome home.
You too, Chinatsu, welcome home.
Here I am.
Here we are.
This feels weird.
[gasps]
- Chinatsu.
- Hmm?
Could the two of us
go somewhere on our next day off?
- Where?
- I, uh...
Where should we go?
An amusement park is too obvious, right?
And we already went to the aquarium.
What else is there?
Uh... Shopping for something
I've been wanting to get?
A tracksuit!
I've been wanting to buy a new one!
The one I have is worn out after camp,
so I should replace it!
- [Chinatsu grunts softly]
- What do you say?
Why did I say "tracksuit"?
That's not exactly sexy.
- Sure.
- Are you serious?
But in return, there's a cafe
that I've been wanting to stop by.
Could we go check it out?
Uh... yeah, for sure.
Sounds great.
How about next Saturday?
- You have practice in the morning, right?
- Yes.
Okay, next Saturday it is.
[thudding]
It's a date!
We're just going to buy a tracksuit,
but it'll be our first outing
since the aquarium, the beach?
And it seemed like
Chinatsu was pretty excited about it too.
You have to get your act together!
Show her what a man you are, Taiki!
This is my chance to tell her how I feel.
Hi, Hina-bean! Let's go have some fun.
What?
- Like, right now?
- We've been cooped up the last three days.
So we gotta go out and make up for it.
[Hina] What about all our stuff?
[Ayame] That's what
coin lockers are for, girl!
When you're going through something,
the best thing you can do
is keep yourself from thinking about it.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Hina] That doesn't really look like me.
[Ayame] Come on, that's what makes it fun!
Oh, that shade looks stunning on you.
[Hina] I've never actually
worn lipstick before.
Then we'll buy one sometime.
Yeah. Let's.
Hockey! Let's do air hockey next!
I've never played though.
[Ayame] What?
This is 20% of the joy in life.
[Hina] 20%?
[Ayame] And FYI,
the seasonal Häagen-Dazs flavors are 50%.
[Hina] I've somehow missed
70% of life's joy.
[Ayame] Let's reclaim that 20%.
Here we go!
- [Hina exclaims]
- [game chiming]
[exclaims] That's how it's done.
[Hina] You're not gonna
let me enjoy this, are you?
Ha!
[chuckles] Take that!
[game chiming]
- Winner!
- [Hina grunting angrily]
TAIKO MAESTRO
BEAT IT
[Ayame] You've done this one?
- [Hina] Punch it, punch it!
- [Ayame whimpers]
[both exclaiming]
[Hina groans]
[Ayame] What a relief.
Looks like she's cheered up a bit.
I'm gonna make sure
she has a blast tonight.
- [boy] Ayame? Is that you?
- Uh?
Oh, what, you know this chick?
She's pretty hot.
My ex-girlfriend.
[sighs]
Wait, are you an idiot, man?
Why'd you end things with her?
Well...
Let me tell you,
she kind of has
this "princess" thing going on.
She got on me for everything.
How I talk to cashiers...
She always told me
I don't enunciate enough when I order.
What I was looking for
was something more casual.
[Ayame] He may have been a little awkward,
but I thought he was a nice guy.
[boy] She wasn't the girl
I thought she was gonna be, you know?
[Ayame] I wasn't a good judge
of character, I guess.
Why don't we go?
[boy] None of your relationships last,
huh, not just with me?
Your older sister
has a handsome boyfriend, right?
You should follow her example
and be more considerate of--
- Listen!
- Think you're right all you want.
It's what keeps you going, isn't it?
Huh?
If you really believe what you're saying,
then you're not a good judge of character.
If you convince yourself
that you're the rational one
and the one who dumped you
is crazy and made the wrong choice,
then all the time you spent
loving the other person
doesn't have to feel like it was a waste.
[sobs]
[gasps]
[grunts angrily] And, dude,
I'll leak your secret social media profile
if you come at me again!
[boy] No, not that!
- I'm sorry.
- Not at all.
You did nothing wrong, Hina-bean.
Not a single thing.
EIMEI PRIVATE HIGH SCHOOL
[grunts]
[sighs]
- [grunts]
- Whoopsies, my bad!
Hey, was that on purpose?
Take these! I need help
getting them into the storage room.
Yes, ma'am.
[Taiki] Ever since the training camp,
it seems like you've been mad at me.
If I did something wrong, then...
It was nothing in particular.
[Taiki] It was something, all right.
[Ayame] It's just...
Hina-bean was crying, you know?
I know.
What do you mean you know?!
Whatever pain you think she's feeling,
it's probably 100 times worse than that.
And you act like
it doesn't bother you-- [gasps]
I get it,
but given how things are right now,
I can't just go up and talk to her.
I've told her where I stand on things.
All I can do now
is wait for her to decide what to do next.
It would be selfish of me to ask her
to go back to being my friend.
[Ayame] So Inota does care for her
in his own way.
Just not romantically.
I don't get it.
Why you would turn down
someone like Hina-bean in the first place?
This person you have feelings for,
are they really that great?
[gasps]
Hey!
Practice is about to start.
Got it!
[Taiki] What kind of question is that?
If my answer was yes, it would
make it sound like Hina isn't great.
[Kyo grunts]
What?
It's nothing.
If I had to guess,
you think I'm meddling
in other people's business, huh?
That face says I'm totally right.
I may be an outsider in all of this.
But seeing Hina that upset and crying,
it made me want to know why.
And I always tell it like it is!
Unapologetically.
Because that's who I am! Deal with it!
I don't care what anybody thinks about me.
However they see me, that's on them.
[sighs]
But, you know,
I do think you've been a life raft,
keeping Hina afloat through some of this.
So having someone like you isn't all bad.
[exclaims softly]
[Ayame] You're a bit condescending,
you know that?
- First time I've heard that.
- Huh?
Uh, what's that?
[Hina] Lil' Bunny Ears.
We made it for the Cultural Festival.
It's a trick I use sometimes.
Blacking out my vision helps me to focus.
All righty then, Hina.
We'll just postpone your turn.
[groans, sniffles]
I wish I could just blow up the gym.
I didn't want to skip practice
because I got rejected.
But being in the same space
with Taiki and Chinatsu,
I feel like I can't breathe.
[indistinct chatter]
[Taiki] Kyo! Have you seen
my phone anywhere?
[Kyo] You left it on that chair earlier.
[Taiki] Oh, yeah, there it is. Thanks!
[boy] Hey, Taiki! Let's get some food.
[Taiki] Sorry, I'm busy!
See you later! Bye!
Whoa, what's up with Taiki?
Why was he in such a hurry?
Maybe he's got a date.
[Nishida] What?!
- Chill out, man, I'm just joking around.
- [Nishida] You better be!
He, of all people,
would never betray me like that!
[Haryu] Hmm?
Wait. He does?
I mean, it's not like he told me
that it's actually happening, but...
Do you think he's going out with...
Probably.
[laughs]
I've been wondering
how long he was gonna stew on that.
It's more like him
to just leap and let the net appear.
[Taiki panting]
[pleasant music playing]
In front of the planters,
in front of the planters.
[gasps]
[boy] You see that girl back there?
She's cute.
What are you looking at?
Well, uh...
I was thinking that
the clouds are moving fast today.
[music fades]
[closing theme song playing]